[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie Jaws scared so many people that the beach attendance was down in the summer of 1975.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It has an unemployment rate  of 15%. According to the 2000 Census it is the poorest of   the 100 largest US Cities.  Which city is it?", "correct_answer": "Detroit", "incorrect_answers": ["Newark", "New Haven", "Boca Raton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "I am from a country in Central Europe. Which domain name do I most likely type to access pages in my native language?", "correct_answer": ".pl", "incorrect_answers": [".pg", ".pk", ".pa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The ending of what Steven Spielberg movie takes place at Devils Tower?", "correct_answer": "Close Encounters of the Third Kind", "incorrect_answers": ["E.T: The Extra-Terrestrial", "Raiders of the Lost Ark", "Saving Private Ryan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What song composed by Elton John for the movie The Lion King won the 1994 Academy Award for Best Original Song?", "correct_answer": "Can You Feel the Love Tonight", "incorrect_answers": ["Circle of Life", "I Just Cant Wait to Be King", "Youll Be in My Heart"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cloning, the process of creating an identical copy of an organism, is only attainable by artificial means.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Craigs love interest in the movie Next Friday?", "correct_answer": "Karla", "incorrect_answers": ["Pinky", "Lisa", "Dwana"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The largest ant colony is located on the Ishikari coast of Hokkaido. Approximately how many ants are there in this colony?", "correct_answer": "300,000,000", "incorrect_answers": ["30,000,000", "700,000,000", "1,500,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who delivered the following movie quote: Im gonna change you from a rooster to a hen with one shot!!?", "correct_answer": "Dolly Parton to Dabney Coleman", "incorrect_answers": ["Clint Eastwood to Eli Wallach", "Lily Tomlin to Dabney Coleman", "Jane Fonda to Dabney Coleman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many calories (kcal) is equivalent to one pound?", "correct_answer": "3500", "incorrect_answers": ["1000", "2500", "2000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The white pages are a telephone directory listing of the telephone numbers of these entities.", "correct_answer": "Ordinary subscribers", "incorrect_answers": ["Government officials", "Businessmen", "Policemen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The White Snake is a fairy tale included in the collection of fairy tales by this author.", "correct_answer": "Brothers Grimm", "incorrect_answers": ["Andrew Lang", "Oscar Wilde", "Hans Christian Andersen"]}]